Guide to the World Student Christian Federation Europe Region Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- WSCF Interregional Records, Series V
  - 5.15.4 Interregional correspondence with other regions: North America, Asia/Pacific, 1994-1996 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 5.16.1 WSCF General Assembly - Chantilly, France, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 5.16.2 WSCF General Assembly - Chantilly, France, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - 5.16.3 WSCF General Assembly - Yamoussoukro, Cote d'Ivoire, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - 5.16.4 WSCF General Assembly - Yamoussoukro, Cote d'Ivoire, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 5.17.1 WSCF General Assembly - Beirut, Lebanon, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 5.17.2 WSCF General Assembly - Chiang Mai, Thailand, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 5.17.2 WSCF General Assembly - Chiang Mai, Thailand, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 5.18.1 Interregional program reports and minutes: WSCF Annual Reports, 1978-1990 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 5.18.2 Interregional program reports and minutes: WSCF Programme Reports, 1979-1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 5.18.3 Interregional program reports and minutes: WSCF Directories, 1982, 1987, no date (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 5.18.4 Interregional program reports and minutes: General Assembly minutes - San Francisco, Mexico, Chantilly, 1981, 1986, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 5.18.5 Interregional program reports and minutes: Executive Committee and Officers' meetings, 1981-1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 5.18.6 Interregional program reports and minutes: "Before the Cock Crows" publication, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - WSCF Archives and History Project, 1991-1994 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Participation of Orthodox movements in WSCF 1895-1972, ca. 1972 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Orthodox consultations, reports, 1992-1997 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - WSCF Women's Commission, 1984-2002 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Projects / Working Groups, Series VI
  - Theological Project
    - 6.1.1 Theological Reflection, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - 6.1.2 Orthodox Project, 1972-1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - 6.1.3 Documents, 1980-1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - 6.1.4 Minutes, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - 6.1.5 Minutes, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 6.1.6 Minutes, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 6.1.7 Minutes, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 6.1.8 Minutes, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - 6.1.9 Minutes, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 6.2.1 Minutes, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 6.2.2 Minutes, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 6.2.3 Minutes, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - 6.2.4 Minutes, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - 6.2.5 Minutes, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - 6.3.1 Correspondence, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - 6.3.2 Correspondence, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - 6.3.3 Correspondence, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - 6.3.4 Correspondence, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 6.3.5 Correspondence, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - 6.3.6 Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 6.4.1 Conferences - CPED, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 6.4.2 Conferences - Cartigny, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - 6.4.3 Conferences - Liebfrauenberg, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - 6.4.4 Conferences - Agape, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - 6.4.5 Conferences - Cartigny, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - 6.5.1 Darmstadt/Gollwitzer - Darmstadt Assembly, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - 6.5.2 Darmstadt/Gollwitzer - Gollwizer Seminar, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - 6.5.3 Darmstadt/Gollwitzer - Darmstadt Follow-up, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - 6.6.1 Haugtun Conference - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - 6.6.2 Haugtun Conference - Finance, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - 6.6.3 Haugtun Conference - Conference documents, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - 6.6.4 Haugtun Conference - Preparatory papers, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - 6.6.5 Haugtun Conference - Participants, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - 6.6.6 Haugtun Conference - Preparatory work, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - 6.7.1 Conferences - Agape, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - 6.7.2 Conferences - Agape, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - 6.7.3 Conferences - Agape, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - 6.8.1 Vienna - Theology Born of Experience - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - 6.8.2 Vienna - Theology Born of Experience - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - 6.8.3 Vienna - Theology Born of Experience - Preparatory papers, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 6.8.4 Vienna - Theology Born of Experience - Follow-up, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - 6.8.5 Bulgaria / Greece visit, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - 6.8.6 Bulgaria / Greece visit - Follow-up, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - 6.9.1 Darbu, Norway Conference - Preparatory papers, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - 6.9.2 Darbu, Norway Conference - Invitations, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - 6.9.3 Darbu, Norway Conference- Forms, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - 6.9.4 Darbu, Norway Conference - Participants, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - 6.9.5 Darbu, Norway Conference - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 6.9.6 Darbu, Norway Conference - Finances, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - 6.9.7 Darbu, Norway Conference - Minutes, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - 6.9.8 Darbu, Norway Conference - Reports and papers, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - 6.10.1 "CASA Cares" Conference, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - 6.10.2 "CASA Cares" Conference, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - 6.10.3 Bodenfelde Conference, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Reports, 1982, 1987, 1989, 1991, 1993, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Additional documents, 1977-1990 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Women's Project
    - 6.11.1 Correspondence, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - 6.11.2 Correspondence, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - 6.11.3 Correspondence, 1978 Jan-May (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - 6.11.4 Correspondence, 1978 May-Dec (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - 6.11.5 Correspondence, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - 6.11.6 Correspondence, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - 6.11.7 Correspondence, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - 6.12.1 Mailings from other women's groups, 1982-1987 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - 6.12.2 Address lists, 1982-1987 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - 6.12.3 Correspondence, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - 6.12.4 Correspondence, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - 6.12.5 Correspondence, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - 6.12.6 Correspondence, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - 6.12.7 Correspondence, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - 6.12.8 Correspondence, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - 6.13.1 Working Group minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - 6.13.2 Working Group minutes, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - 6.13.3 Working Group minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - 6.13.4 Working Group minutes, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - 6.13.5 Working Group minutes, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - 6.13.6 Working Group minutes, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - 6.13.7 Working Group minutes, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - 6.13.8 Working Group minutes, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - 6.13.9 Working Group minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - 6.14.1 Conferences: Orthodox Consultation, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - 6.14.2 Conferences: New Heaven New Earth, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - 6.14.3 Conferences: Velletri, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - 6.14.4 Conferences: European Middle East meeting, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - 6.14.5 Conferences: Consultation Brussels, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - 6.14.6 Conferences: Russell Tribunal, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - 6.14.7 Conferences: General, 1974-1983 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - 6.14.8 Conferences: Haugtun, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - 6.14.9 Conferences: Linho, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - 6.14.10 Conferences: El Escorial, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - 6.14.11 Conferences: GDR visit, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - 6.15.1 Conferences: Corrymeela - preparation, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - 6.15.2 Conferences: Corrymeela - conference centre, programme, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - 6.15.3 Conferences: Corrymeela - participants, finance, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - 6.15.4 Conferences: Corrymeela - reports, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - 6.15.5 Conferences: Women's Seminar, Uppsala, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - 6.15.6 Conferences: Women's Commission - Manila, New York, 1984, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - 6.15.7 Conferences: Women's Commission - papers, 1985-1988 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - 6.15.8 Conferences: Women's Commission - papers, 1985-1988 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - 6.15.9 Conferences: Women's Commission - papers, 1985-1988 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - 6.16.1 Resources: Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - 6.16.2 Resources: Conferences, 1982-1987 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - 6.16.3 Resources: Finance, 1977-1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - 6.16.4 Resources: Info about movements, 1978-1980 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - 6.16.5 Resources: Frontier Internship in Mission (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - 6.16.6 Resources: ISIS, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - 6.16.7 Resources: World YWCA, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - 6.16.8 Resources: Bibliographies (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - 6.16.9 Resources: Available materials (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - 6.16.10 Resources: Study centres / organisations (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - 6.16.11 Resources: Who has what? (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - 6.16.12 Resources: Center for Women and Religion, Graduate Theological Union, 1977-1980 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - 6.16.13 Resources: Women's kit (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - 6.16.14 Resources: ordered (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - 6.16.15 Resources: received (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - 6.17.1 Correspondence with other regions: Africa, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - 6.17.2 Correspondence with other regions: Asia, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - 6.17.3 Correspondence with other regions: Latin America, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - 6.17.4 Correspondence with other regions: Europe, 1984-1988 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - 6.17.5 Christianity: Women and the Church -I, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - 6.17.6 Christianity: Women and the Church - II, 1977-1981 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - 6.17.7 Christianity: Women and ordination, 1980s (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - 6.17.8 Christianity: Women and worship, 1980s (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - 6.18.1 Christianity: Women and the Bible, 1980s (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - 6.18.2 Christianity: Feminist theology - I, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - 6.18.3 Christianity: Feminist theology - II, 1975-1978 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - 6.18.4 Christianity: Bible studies, 1970s (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - 6.18.5 Christianity: Mary Condren - I, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - 6.18.6 Christianity: Mary Condren - II, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - 6.18.7 Society: Women and power, 1970s/1980s (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - 6.18.8 Society: Women and religion, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 6.18.9 Society: Women and education, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - 6.18.10 Society: Women and peace work, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - 6.18.11 Society: Women and development, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - 6.19.1 Society: Women and culture, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - 6.19.2 Society: Women and political systems, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - 6.19.3 Society: Women and law, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - 6.19.4 Society: Women and work, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - 6.19.5 Society: Women in Portugal, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - 6.19.6 Society: Women in specific countries, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - 6.19.7 Society: Women and language, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - 6.19.8 Society: Women and housework, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - 6.19.9 Society: What are women?, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - 6.19.10 Society: Women and lifestyles, 1970s-1980s (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - 6.19.11 Society: Women and their bodies - I, 1970s/1980s (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - 6.19.12 Society: Women and their bodies - II, 1970s/1980s (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - 6.19.13 Society: Women's liberation movement, 1970s/1980s (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Women's Working Group
    - 6.20.1 Minutes, reports, resources, 1979-1983 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - 6.20.2 Minutes, reports, resources, 1984-1990 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - 6.20.3 Compilation file, 1976-1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 6.21.1 Agape conference, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - 6.21.2 Strasbourg conference, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - 6.21.3 Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Additional correspondence, reports, newsletter, 1991-1994 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Hardanger Months
    - 6.22.1 Correspondence, reports, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - 6.22.2 Correspondence, reports, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - 6.22.3 Correspondence, reports, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, reports, application, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Refugee Project
    - 6.23.1 Conferences, meetings, memos, 1976-1979 (Box 5)
    - 6.23.2 Conferences, meetings, memos, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - 6.23.3 Correspondence, 1978-1986 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - 6.24.1 Correspondence, 1977-1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 6.24.2 Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - 6.24.3 Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - 6.24.4 Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Solidarity Working Group
    - Reports, 1987, 1989, 1991, 1993, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Programmatic Working Group
    - Minutes, correspondence, newsletters, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Working Document, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Publications Working Group
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - The Latin Project
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Reports, conference at Sete, France "Minorities Protestantes et Culture Latine", 1986 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, reports, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Reports, conference in Malaga, Spain, "L'Autre Europe", 1988 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, reports, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Lingua Franca (East European Language and Leadership Training Project)
    - Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, reports, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Financial records, correspondence, requests for funds, 1992-1994 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Project Coordinator contract, correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Project Coordinator contract, correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Financial records, correspondence, requests for funds, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Reports, planning, newsletter, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Courses, teacher training, evaluation forms, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Financial records, correspondence, requests for funds, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Reports, planning, newsletter, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Courses, teacher training, evaluation forms -Belarus, Romania, Poland, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Courses, teacher training, evaluation forms - Belarus, Romania, Poland, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Project Coordinator contracts, correspondence, reports, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Financial records, correspondence, requests for funds, 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Reports, planning, newsletter, 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Language courses, teacher training, publicity, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Language courses, teacher training, publicity, 1997-1998 (Box 69)
    - Youth Worker Management Traing Course, Slovakia, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Archives Project
    - Notes and correspondence re. organization of WSCF Europe Region archives, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Correspondence With Other Organizations, Series VII
  - 8.1 Cimade, IUS, AEYSC, Syndesmos, IAEL, WUS, 1977-1986 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 8.1 Cimade, IUS, AEYSC, Syndesmos, IAEL, WUS, 1977-1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - 8.1 Cimade, IUS, AEYSC, Syndesmos, IAEL, WUS, 1977-1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - 8.1 Cimade, IUS, AEYSC, Syndesmos, IAEL, WUS, 1977-1986 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - 8.1 Cimade, IUS, AEYSC, Syndesmos, IAEL, WUS, 1977-1986 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - 8.2 CEPPLE, CPC, Laity in the Church, HKH, LAY Academies, ICYE, LWF, 1977-1986 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - 8.2 CEPPLE, CPC, Laity in the Church, HKH, LAY Academies, ICYE, LWF, 1977-1986 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - 8.2 CEPPLE, CPC, Laity in the Church, HKH, LAY Academies, ICYE, LWF, 1977-1986 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - 8.2 CEPPLE, CPC, Laity in the Church, HKH, LAY Academies, ICYE, LWF, 1977-1986 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - 8.3 NCFYO, LSU, COELI, Christians for Socialism, Pax Christi, 1976-1986 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - 8.3 NCFYO, LSU, COELI, Christians for Socialism, Pax Christi, 1976-1986 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - 8.4 Pax Christi, WCC, WCC Youth, CWME, Faith and Witness, 1978-1990 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - 8.4 Pax Christi, WCC, WCC Youth, CWME, Faith and Witness, 1978-1990 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - 8.4 Pax Christi, WCC, WCC Youth, CWME, Faith and Witness, 1978-1990 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - 8.5 ISMUM, International Mob: For Survival, El Salvador Info, Vluchtelingenwerk Netherlands, Cimade, WUS, WFDY, 1981-1989 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 8.5 ISMUM, International Mob: For Survival, El Salvador Info, Vluchtelingenwerk Netherlands, Cimade, WUS, WFDY, 1981-1989 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 8.5 ISMUM, International Mob: For Survival, El Salvador Info, Vluchtelingenwerk Netherlands, Cimade, WUS, WFDY, 1981-1989 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - 8.6 European Youth Foundation, 1973-1979 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - 8.6 European Youth Foundation, 1973-1979 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - 8.6 European Youth Foundation, 1973-1979 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - 8.6 European Youth Foundation, 1973-1979 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - 8.7 European Youth Foundation, 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 8.7 European Youth Foundation, 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - 8.7 European Youth Foundation, 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - 8.7 European Youth Foundation, 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - 8.8 European Youth Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - 8.8 European Youth Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - 8.8 European Youth Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - 8.8 European Youth Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - 8.9 European Youth Centre, 1981-1985 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - 8.9 European Youth Centre, 1981-1985 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - 8.9 European Youth Centre, 1981-1985 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - 8.9 European Youth Centre, 1981-1985 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - 8.10 European Youth Centre, 1986-1989 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - 8.10 European Youth Centre, 1986-1989 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - 8.10 European Youth Centre, 1986-1989 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - 8.11 Ecumenical Youth Council in Europe, 1977-1982 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - 8.11 Ecumenical Youth Council in Europe, 1977-1982 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - 8.11 Ecumenical Youth Council in Europe, 1977-1982 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - 8.12 Frontier Internship in Mission, 1981-1984 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - 8.12 Frontier Internship in Mission, 1981-1984 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - 8.12 Frontier Internship in Mission, 1981-1984 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - 8.12 Frontier Internship in Mission, 1981-1984 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - 8.13 Conference of European Churches, Commission on InterChurch Aid: Refugee and World Service, 1978-1985 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - 8.13 Conference of European Churches, Commission on InterChurch Aid: Refugee and World Service, 1978-1985 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - 8.13 Conference of European Churches, Commission on InterChurch Aid: Refugee and World Service, 1978-1985 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - 8.13 Conference of European Churches, Commission on InterChurch Aid: Refugee and World Service, 1978-1985 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - 8.14 Conference of European Churches, Churches Human Rights Program, 1972-1985 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - 8.14 Conference of European Churches, Churches Human Rights Program, 1972-1985 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - 8.14 Conference of European Churches, Churches Human Rights Program, 1972-1985 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - 8.14 Conference of European Churches, Churches Human Rights Program, 1972-1985 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - 8.15 Ecumenical Research Exchange, 1980-1984 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - 8.15 Ecumenical Research Exchange, 1980-1984 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - 8.15 Ecumenical Research Exchange, 1980-1984 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - 8.16 JECI-MIEC, KAG-AGG, JOC, 1976-1989 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - 8.16 JECI-MIEC, KAG-AGG, JOC, 1976-1989 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - 8.16 JECI-MIEC, KAG-AGG, JOC, 1976-1989 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - 8.17 Correspondence with interpreters, 1982-1990 (Box 51A, Folder 1)
  - 8.17 Frontier Internship in Mission, 1995, n.d. (Box 51A, Folder 2)
  - 8.17 Frontier Internship in Mission, 1993-1995 (Box 51A, Folder 3)
  - 8.17 Frontier Internship in Mission, 1988-1989 (Box 51A, Folder 4)
  - 8.17 Frontier Internship in Mission, 1985-1988 (Box 51A, Folder 5)
  - 8.18 EYCE, Syndesmos, YCW/JOC, YCF, IMCS, 1987-1993 (Box 51A, Folder 6)
  - 8.18 EYCE, Syndesmos, YCW/JOC, YCF, IMCS, 1988-1991 (Box 51A, Folder 7)
  - 8.18 EYCE, Syndesmos, YCW/JOC, YCF, IMCS, IVS, World Student Festival, World Student Forum, 1986-1994 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - 8.18 EYCE, Syndesmos, YCW/JOC, YCF, IMCS, IVS, World Student Festival, World Student Forum, 1986-1994 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - 8.18 EYCE, Syndesmos, YCW/JOC, YCF, IMCS, IVS, World Student Festival, World Student Forum, 1986-1994 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - 8.19 CEC, 1986-2003 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - 8.19 CEC, 1986-2003 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - 8.19 CEC, 1986-2003 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - 8.19 CEC, 1986-2003 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Administrative and Fundraising Records
  - Human Resources (Staff)
    - 9.1 Hiring of European Regional Secretary and intern work contracts, 1987-1989 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - 9.1 Applications for Lingua Franca coordinator, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - 9.1 Applications for Regional Secretary, 2000 (Box 53)
  - Fundraising
    - 9.2 Correspondence, requests, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - 9.2 Correspondence, requests, 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 9.2 Correspondence, requests, 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - 9.2 Big E funding, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - 9.2 Conference of European Churches requests; Senior Friends, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - 9.2 Correspondence, requests, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - 9.2 Correspondence, requests, 1997-1999 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 9.2 Correspondence, requests, 1997-1999 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - 9.2 Applications to European Commission, 1996-2000 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 9.2 Correspondence, requests, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - 9.2 Correspondence, requests, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Donor correspondence
    - 9.3 EYF, Youth for Europe, grants, reports, correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - 9.3 EYF, correspondence, reports, applications, 1993-1996 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - 9.3 EYF, Youth for Europe, grants, reports, correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - 9.3 European Commission, Youth for Europe, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - 9.3 Donor letters, 1991, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - 9.3 European Youth Centre, 1991-1996 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Project funding
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - Conference of European Churches, Commission of the European Communities, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - United States churches, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - Swedish, Dutch, Finnish churches, 1991 (Box 55, Folder system_indicator_4460d83ccff38ba25e606ca7bba32975)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - CEC and others, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - CEC and others, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - Commission of the European Communities, WCC, Youth Bureau, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - U.S. and European churches, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - European Commission, Youth Bureau, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - U.S. and European churches, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 12)